mongoosemetrics.com 2008-01-01

# Mongoose Metrics.com About Your Privacy

This policy applies to Mongoose Metrics, and its subsidiaries which are referred to here collectively as Mongoose Metrics. At Mongoose Metrics, the security and integrity of our customers' personal information is important to us. We take every reasonable measure necessary to protect the privacy of our customers while providing the high level communication services they expect. 

Mongoose Metrics's privacy practices are in accordance with all federal and provincial laws and regulations and where applicable with the privacy rules established by the Federal Trade Commission (FTC). 

Mongoose Metrics has in place privacy and security practices to safeguard our customers' personal information. These practices are reviewed, and if necessary revised, on a regular basis. Additionally, Mongoose Metrics' employees receive privacy training and must comply with Mongoose Metrics privacy practices as a condition of employment. 

Personal information collected by Mongoose Metrics is information about an identifiable individual that may include such information as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, financial information, birth date and any recorded complaints. 

At Mongoose Metrics, we collect customer information for one or more of the following purposes: 

  * To provide a positive customer experience, and deliver, bill for, and collect payment for products and services; 
  * To understand customer requirements and make information available regarding products and services offered by Mongoose Metrics and its agents, dealers and related companies; 
  * To manage and develop Mongoose Metrics business and operations; 
  * To meet legal and regulatory requirements; and 
  * To obtain credit information or provide it to others. 

Mongoose Metrics does not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. 

Mongoose Metrics retains personal information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 

Mongoose Metrics informs customers of the existence, use and disclosure of their personal information upon request and gives them access to their information. 

Mongoose Metrics ensures that customer information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Customers can challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and request amendments as appropriate. 

Mongoose Metrics companies share information with other Mongoose Metrics companies, in order to offer customers products and services that they may find attractive. Notices on sharing information are contained in each company's application forms, invoices and web sites. If customers do not want to be marketed with these products and services, they can contact Mongoose Metrics (see How To Contact Mongoose Metrics below). 

Additional information on your privacy is located in the Frequently Asked Questions section of [http://www.mongoosemetrics.com](http://www.mongoosemetrics.com/) under the Category of Privacy. 

Customers that wish to: 

  * obtain more information about Mongoose Metrics Commitment to Privacy; 
  * access, or obtain more information about, their personal information held by Mongoose Metrics; or 
  * make a privacy-related complaint; 

may contact a Mongoose Metrics customer service representative. 

Mongoose Metrics  
Modified October 1, 2007
